地方检察官给出的交易是有期徒刑一年
That's the deal the D.A's offering. One year.
二级性侵犯
Second degree sexual assault.
我本以为我们可以胜诉
l thought you said we could win this.
我知道你担心你的妻子和女儿
l know you're worried about your wife and daughter.
但是判刑一年总好过十年
But one year in jail is a lot better than ten.
马蒂在哪
So where's Marty?
他退休了  法林先生  他让我问候您
He's retiring, Mr. Fallin. He sends his regards.
肯  这是我儿子尼古拉斯
Oh, Ken, this is my son Nicholas.
- 你好  - 很高兴认识你
- Hi. - Um, pleasure.
马蒂离开了 我很遗憾
Well, I'm sorry to hear that Marty's leaving.
我们合作有三十年了
He, uh, he had our account for thirty years.
法林先生  有一个小问题
Mr. Fallin, we have a slight problem.
我们额外给您增加的一 百万信贷额度两周前已经到期了
That extra million we extended on your credit facility was due two weeks ago.
好吧  我们没有任何问题  只是在等收完账
Well, we're good for that. We're just waiting for some  receivables.
恕我直言  这也不是我们的问题
With all due respect, that's not our problem.
肯  作为一个新手  我很欣赏你
Ken, I appreciate that you're new with the bank.
想要给老板留下好印象
Wanna impress the bosses.
但是  呃 强迫客户在我们这儿行不通
But, uh... we're not exactly in the game of strong-arming our clients.
法林先生  我的上司派我来
Mr. Fallin, my bosses sent me here.
事实上是他们不愿意参与到这个
Truth of the matter is, they don't want to be in the business
为欠款的客户提供融资的业务中
of financing your delinquent clients.
所以
So...
我希望我们能在周末之前处理完这件事
l hope we can take care of this by the end of the week.
好吧  呃  替我给马蒂问好
Yeah, well, uh... Say hi to Marty.
好吧  他有一点说的是对的
Well, he has a point.
我的意思是  我们不能再放任这些人了
l mean, we can't keep Ietting these people slide.
他们是我们的老客户  尼古拉斯
They're old clients, Nicholas.
他们欠我们一百万美元
They owe us a million dollars.
你的朋友杰德·托宾也在这些人中
Your friend Jed Tobin is one of 'em.
你要跟他说他已经晚六个月了吗
You want to tell him he's six months late?
尼克  看这个新的木星推杆
Hey, Nick. Did you see this new Jupiter putter?
- 没有  - 碳素钢身  完美的平衡
- No. - Carbon steel. Perfectly balanced.
设计者是有史以来最顶级的推杆设计师之一
The guy that designed it is like one of the top putter designers of all time.
太丑了
lt's very ugly.
- 你打过奥克芒吗  - 没有
- You ever play Oakmont? - No.
- 想打吗  - 并不怎么想
- You want to? - Not really.
不  尼克  木星公司的人已经安排好了
No, Nick. No, the guys from Jupiter have set it up
作为对我们这段时间认真工作的答谢
as a thank-you for all the good work we're doing.
那你去吧
Oh, you play.
尼克  是奥克芒啊
Nick. Oakmont!
如果你还需要队友  阿尔文·马斯特森说他打得也不错
lf you need a fourth, Alvin Masterson says he's a decent golfer.
阿尔文吗  那家伙打的太差了
Alvin? That guy's got a terrible slice.
去几楼  哥儿们
What floor, buddy?
五楼
5.
衣服不错
That's a nice suit.
谢谢
Thank you.
我也不喜欢有人在电梯里跟我聊天
l don't like it either when people talk to me in an elevator.
- 你在这做什么  - 什么
- What are you doing here? - Excuse me?
不是你  是他
Not you. Him.
- 路易莎  - 请出去
- Louisa. - Please leave.
我只是想和你说几句话
l just... I want to talk to you.
赶紧给我滚出去
Get the hell outta here!
- 呃  先生  你  - 别管闲事
- Uh... sir, you... you... - Stay outta this.
他走了吗
ls he gone?
恩  你还好吗
Yeah. You all right?
还好  呃  卢卡斯·法尔在你的办公室  他二十岁
Yeah. Uh... in your office. Lucas Farr. He's twenty years old.
昨天社会服务部门把他弟弟接走了
Social Services took his younger brothers out of his care yesterday.
所以来参加今天下午的听证会
So the shelter hearing's this afternoon.
这个人  怎么回事
Yeah... uh... this guy... what...
是我爸爸
lt's my father.
我有事  先忙了
I've got a lot to do.
法外真情
第三季  第五集
翻译   大淘  子
校对  油 球
特效  转轮 枪
我妈妈三年前死于癌症
My mother died three years ago-- cancer.
还有  呃  我爸爸一直都不在
And, uh... my dad's been gone forever.
所以就只剩下我和两个弟弟
So it's just me and my two brothers.
嗯
Okay.
那个  昨天晚上有人敲门
So... Iast night there's this knock at the door
之后社会服务部门的人就带着一个警察进来了
and some woman from Social Services comes in with a cop,
然后他们带走了约翰和格伦
and they take John and Glenn.
据说你把你的弟弟们锁在房间里
Says here you locked your brothers in the apartment.
我要出去工作  总没办法一直找人照顾他们吧
Well, I can't always find people to look after them when I go to work, right?
那你在哪里工作
Where do you work?
在巴基的咖啡店  在北街
At Bucky's Coffee. It's on the North Side.
这上面说  你弟弟在房间里玩烟花
lt says that your brothers were lighting fireworks inside the apartment
还从五楼的窗户扔燃烧的纸团
and dropping burning rolls of toilet paper from the fifth story window.
那应该是格伦  他会有一些小毛病
That would be Glenn. He's got some problems.
现在他在一所特殊学校上学
He's enrolled in a special needs school.
他不是反应迟钝
He's not retarded.
他只是在阅读上有一些障碍
He's just got problems with reading, you know?
是注意力的问题
lt's attention stum.
好吧  很明显你不能把他们锁在屋子里
Well, clearly you can't lock them in an apartment.
这也不安全
lt's just not safe.
我知道的  好吧  我又不傻
l know that, okay? l mean, I'm not stupid.
只是  我必须工作
lt's just... I have to go to work,
而且我现在雇不起保姆
and I cannot amord to pay a babysitter right now.
好吧  下午会有一个关于监护权的听证会
Well, there's a shelter hearing this afternoon.
我们试试看能不能解决这个问题
We'll see what we can try and work out.
那些社会服务部门的人
Listen, these guys from Social Services
一直跟邻居们打听
are walking around talking to the neighbors
而且  你要知道  整栋楼里的人都在说
and, you know, like, people in the building are talking about
我是如何像利波拉斯一样和男人进进出出
how I'm like Liberace with the men coming in and out.
完全是没有的事
lt's totally untrue.
你的私生活是属于你自己的
Well, your private life is your own.
当然是
Yeah, of course it is.
只要你在你的弟弟们面前注意言行举止
As long as you conduct yourself appropriately in front of your brothers.
我弟弟们都知道我是同性恋  好吗
My brothers know that I'm gay, okay?
没关系的
lt doesn't matter.
- 好吧  - 你说的好吧是什么意思
- Okay. - Whadaya mean, okay?
如果你不想帮我  我可以直接找一个真正的律师
You know if you're not into this, l can just go get a real lawyer.
我男朋友就是一个很厉害的律师
My boyfriend's an expensive lawyer.
我只是不想因为这些小事打扰他
l just don't feel like bothering him with something like this.
好吧  如果你想找人换了我  那就换吧
Right. Well, if you want to replace me, then just replace me.
别怕伤了我的感情
Don't bother sparing my feelings.
好吧
All right.
听着  如果你能解决这个问题  我也可以不找他
Look... if you think you can handle this, l won't call him.
尼克
Nick.
嘿  呃  很抱歉  关于我爸爸的事
Hey, um... Sorry about that... l mean, with my father.
说来话长
lt's kind of a long story.
没关系
lt's fine.
不说这个  听着  我有一个想法
Anyway, listen, l, uh... l have this idea about, uh...
也许可以和你父亲的公司开展一些合作
maybe setting up a relationship with your father's firm.
- 和你的公司  - 合作
- With your firm. - Relationship?
是的  只是领养日的一个无偿的活动
Yeah, it's just a pro bono thing for Adoption Day.
我们需要一家律师事务所来赞助
We need a law firm to sponsor it.
而且  我们一天会促成50组领养
And, uh... we process fifty adoptions in one day.
这是一个非常好  也是非常开心的事情
And it's great. It's really... really a happy thing.
好吧  我会好好考虑一下的
All right. I'll look into it.
太好了  给常感谢
Great. Thanks.
- 你抽烟吗  -不抽
- You smoke? - No.
刚刚  露露有的时候会比较难搞
That was, uh... Lulu can be a hellion sometimes.
作为一个父亲来说  他的孩子这样对他大吼大叫还是挺难堪的
lt's embarrassing for a father to have his kid yell at him like that.
- 好吧  - 遇到困难时她总是和男人一起度过
- Yeah, well, uh... - She's always had a tough time with men.
而且她的妈妈 那是个难搞的
And, her mother... There's a piece o' work.
先生  我得走了  所以
Sir, I have to go, so...
我听说露露结婚了
l heard Lulu got married.
事实上  我还没听说她结婚  就接到了她离婚的消息
Actually, heard she got divorced before I heard she was even married.
我猜这也说得通
Guess that makes sense.
嗯
Right.
呃  萨迪
Uh, Sadie.
亚历克斯的案子怎么样了
How's the Alex Kaller case coming?
还凑合吧  要知道  这事儿挺麻烦
Good. Good. You know, it's a tough one.
他的妻子和女儿
His wife and his daughter.
他受到了侮辱
He's been humiliated.
他欠我们十六万美元
He owes us a hundred and sixty thousand dollars.
什么
What?
好吧  这五个月里他一毛钱也没付过
Well, he hasn't paid a cent in the past five months.
尼克  这家伙因为性侵犯面临着十年牢狱生活
Nick, the guy's facing ten years for sexual assault.
对  好吧  看看你能不能让他把钱付了
Right. Well, just see if you can get him to pay.
法官大人  通常来说我们是不愿意破坏一个家庭的
Normally, Judge Damsen, we don't like to break up a family
但是我们实在不愿意让孩子回到那样的环境中
but we're not comfortable sending the kids back into an environment
回到那个没有人管他们的地方
where they're left unattended.
卢卡斯  你想要负责照顾你的弟弟们吗
Lucas. Do you want to be responsible for your younger brothers?
当然
Yes.
那你就不能把他们扔在家里不管
You cannot leave them unattended.
我见过太多悲剧了
I've seen terrible things happen.
我会努力做得更好
l will do better.
当然  你一定要做得更好
Well, you have to.
我给你一个星期的时间想出解决办法
I'm giving you one week to come up with a plan that works.
而且我警告你  我不喜欢冒险
And I'm warning you, l don't like taking chances.
我雇不起保姆  我没有钱
l can't pay a babysitter. I'm broke.
也许我可以问问我的律师朋友  他也许可以给我一些钱
l can maybe ask that lawyer friend I have. He'll probably just give me the money.
你应该证明你自己能够赚钱给法官看
You should probably just show the Judge you can make the money yourself.
我  你知道的  我实话跟你说
l... you know, I gotta be honest with you.
我对你的态度并不满意
I'm not thrilled with your attitude.
我下次努力
I'll just try harder.
杰德
Jed.
哥们
Dude!
你好
Hey.
见到你太开心了 兄弟
Good to see you, brother dude.
你以前才不会来  这太疯狂了
You never come around, which is insane because the women are insane.
最近在忙什么
Where you been?
嗯  就是一直工作
Well, working. Working.
好吧  所以怎么来了
Yeah. Yeah. Wow. So what's up?
杰德  你的账单  已经逾期了
Well, uh... Jed, your bill is... It's overdue.
什么  我是晚了一个小时没付款吗
What, I'm like an hour late on my payment?
杰德  已经逾期六个月了
lt's six months overdue, Jed.
想想这些年  我多少也有些情面的
Think after all these years, I'd earn a little goodwill.
当然  担任
You do. You do.
如果有问题  你爸爸会自己过来找我说的
Think there's a problem, your father would come down here personally.
杰德  这并不是那么严重的一件事
Jed, it's not... It's not that big a deal.
你和你爸爸是为我工作的  你知道的  对吧
You and your dad work for me. You do know that, right?
多以  就说你到底要不要还钱吧
Well, are you gonna pay, or not?
你要记住  我们一家供你上了法学院
Remember, my family put you through law school.
是我爸爸供我上的法学院
My father put me through law school.
我和我妻子说过了  我们不想做这笔交易
l talked to my wife and, uh... we don't want the deal.
我不会因为莫须有的罪名去坐牢
I'm not going to go to jail for something I didn't do.
我想陪审团会相信我  而且我也知道他们会相信你
l think the jury believes me... and I know they believe you.
那我们就这么办吧
Let's go for it.
- 亚历克斯  - 怎么了
- Alex? - Yeah?
虽然很不好意思
This is very awkward.
但是我的合伙人很担心您的账单问题
My partners are concerned about the status of your bill.
我给过你预付款了
l gave you a retainer.
是的  是的  那钱几个月前就花完了
Right. Right. We burned through that months ago.
好吧
Right.
很抱歉
Sorry.
我一直在担心这件案子  你知道的  我甚至没有来得及看看邮件
Uh... I've been so wrapped up in this, you know, I haven't... even checked the mail.
我今晚会处理好
I'll take care of it tonight.
谢谢
Thank you.
所以  你确定你说的都是真的
So you're sure about all this?
当然
Positive.
我会告诉地方检察官的
I'll let the D.A. know.
尼克  你还记得他吗  亚历克斯·凯勒
Nick, you remember Alex Kaller.
- 亚历克斯  你好  - 你好
- Hey, Alex. - Hi.
- 希望你审讯过程顺利  - 是的  你知道这个过程实在太吓人了
- Good luck with the trial. - Yeah. It's pretty scary, you know?
我真的太害怕了
I'm really scared.
跟他说付费的事了么
Talk to him about the bill?
说了  他说他会解决的
Yeah. He said he'd take care of it.
你好  尼克  我们有弗雷迪·埃文斯了
Oh, hey, Nick. We got Freddy Evans.
- 谁  - 弗雷迪·埃文斯
- Who? - Freddy ''Bam Bam'' Evans.
他签约成了木星高尔夫球队的发言人了
He signed to be Jupiter Golfs spokesman.
我们星期五会约他和他的律师见面  商定签署协议
We're gonna meet Friday with his attorneys and negotiate the endorsement agreement.
- 很好  很好  - 是的
- Great. Great. - Yeah.
所以  奥克芒
So now look... Oakmont.
- 你确定真的不想去  - 我确定
- You sure you don't want to play? - I'm sure.
好吧
All right.
好吧  回去工作
Okay. Well, back to work.
卢卡斯
Lucas.
- 法林先生  - 你怎么在这
- Mr. Fallin. - What're you doing here?
想见我的话  先去法律服务部预约
You want to see me, you make an appointment at Legal Services.
不要直接来这
You don't come here.
好吧  抱歉
Right. Okay. Sorry.
你好
Hey.
你好  呃  要走了吗
Hey. Uh... you leaving?
嗯  是的
Yeah. Yeah.
呃  你也走的话  我们可以一起
Um... well, if you're headed down, I'll ride down with you.
好啊
Yeah.
你会审查代言合同的吧
So you'll review the endorsement contract.
当然  肯定要的
Sure. Sure.
- 太好了  - 嗯
- Terrific. - Okay.
有一个孩子
So there's this kid.
在我周末经常去的咖啡店上班
Works at the coffee shop l go to on weekends.
是个好孩子  身世太惨
Nice kid. Sad story.
所以说  呃  世界真小
Says, uh... small world.
你在处理他的案子是吗
You're-you're working with him at LSP.
是的
Yeah.
- 是卢卡斯吧  - 是的
- Lucas, right? - Right.
是个好孩子
Good kid.
世界是真的小啊
Small world.
你好  很感谢你能过来
Hey. Thanks for coming over.
我只是  呃  只是有点紧张
l just, uh... was a little bit nervous.
- 怎么了  - 可能也不算什么
- What is it? - And it's probably nothing.
但是  我爸爸打电话过来了
But, uh... well, my father's been calling.
我知道  没有留言
And there's nothing, I know.
但是已经十八个未接电话了
But there's eighteen nothings.
好吧
Okay.
你知道的  我爸爸有点
You know, my dad is kind of...
我们之前的关系比较复杂
We just have a strange relationship.
之前也有过这种情况吗
Has he done this before?
有过
Yeah.
但是是很长时间之前了
lt was a long time ago, though.
你先坐一会吧
You want to sit down?
好的
Sure.
听着  我
Look, my...
你是知道的  我妈妈四处厮混
my mother slept around. l mean, you know that.
而且  那时候我爸爸在当海军
And, you know, my dad was in the Navy at that time,
之后  当他发现我妈妈的事情  他就
and when he found out about her affairs, he just was...
好吧
Right.
不管怎样  我并没有想过  或者猜过
Anyway, I don't know, l guess when, you know,
这么多年过去了  他会重新出现在我的生活中
years later, when he came back into my life...
可能我总是会提醒他想起我的母亲
l just always reminded him of my mother... I guess.
怎么会呢
How?
你约了谁吗
You expecting anyone?
是他
lt's him.
你好  阿奇先生
Hi, Mr. Archer.
嗯  现在可能不是你们见面的好时机
Uh, it... it's not a great time.
我只是想和路易莎说句话
l just need a word with Louisa.
但是  现在并不太合适
Well, it's not a great time.
路易莎  我想跟你聊两句
Louisa, I just need to talk to ya!
我说了  现在不行
l said it's not a good time.
等一下
Hold the door
- 早上好  - 早上好
- Hey, 'morning. - Morning.
你收到凯文·埃尔德的生日聚会邀请了吗
So you get the invitation to Kevin Elder's birthday party?
- 嗯  - 你会去吗  我是要去的
- Um... - You going? I'm going.
听说  呃  他们请了花样游泳表演者
Sounds like, uh... They're gonna have synchronized swimmers in the pool.
听起来有点奇怪
Sounds kinda weird.
你会带一个女伴吗
You bringing a date?
- 不带  - 好吧
- No. - Oh.
我打算带珍妮特  一个化妆品销售
I'm bringing that girl Janet from the, uh... cosmetics counter--
莱特斯通百货的  你还记得她吗
Lightstone's. Remember her?
不记得了
Oh.
见到她你就会想起来的
Huh, you will when you see her.
那我们一会  聊一下木星公司的事吧
So uh... we'll just go through that Jupiter stum later.
- 可以  - 好的
- Great. - Great.
尼克  呃
Nick, uh...
奥克芒  反正我是要去的
Oakmont. l mean, I'm gonna play anyway.
你之前跟我说过了
You told me.
好吧
Okay.
好的
Great.
我  呃
l, uh...
我刚刚接到了一个叫哈罗德·施瓦茨的混蛋的电话
l just got om the phone with some jerk named Harold Schwartz.
说他代表杰德·托宾
Claims he's representing Jed Tobin.
代表杰德
Representing Jed?
是的  杰德炒了我们
Yeah, Jed fired us.
- 现在他还威胁要起诉我们  - 他炒了我们
- Now he's threatening to sue us. - He fired us?
- 是啊  说我们有负他的信任  - 你在开玩笑吧
- Yeah. Claims we mismanaged his Trust. - You're kidding.
- 你跟他说什么了  - 什么都没说
- What'd you say to him? - Nothing!
要知道我和他的父亲共事有四十年了
You know I worked with his dad for forty years.
感谢信任  我是他的遗产委托人
I'm Trustee of the kid's estate, for God's sake.
我到他的俱乐部  跟他说他已经逾期了  就说了这个
l walked into his club, and I told him he was late. That's it.
那我们现在要怎么做
So what do we do now?
- 我们可以起诉他  - 不  不行
- We could sue. - No. No.
你再去找他说一下  你再给他一个机会
You go back and see him again. You give him another chance.
路易莎看起来有点喜欢你
Now, Louisa seems to like you...
阿奇先生  别逼我报警  我真的有可能报警的
Mr. Archer, do not force me to call the police. I will call them.
- 你帮我转达几句话给她  - 什么
- You tell her something for me. - What?
告诉她我需要一些钱  就这样
Tell her I need a few bucks, is all.
并不需要一大笔
lt's not a big deal or anything.
我只是  只是需要去买药用
I'm just... It's for some medical problems.
是有不得已的原因才需要的
lt's just for some stum I have to have.
好吧
All right.
你好  我刚刚看你和我爸爸在外边说话
Hey. I saw you talking to my father from the window.
嗯  是的
Yeah.
那他说什么了
And what was he saying?
嗯  他说他有一些医疗上的问题  需要一些钱
Uh, says he has some medical issues... and he needs some money.
好吧
Right.
- 他还给你他电话吗  - 嗯
- Is he still calling you? - Yeah.
露露  要知道  你可以报警的
Well, Lulu, you know, you could talk to the police.
不  我打算  打算给他一些钱
No, I'm just... just gonna give him money.
一般我给完钱他就会走了
He usually goes away when I give him money.
你好  尼克
Hey, Nick.
嗯
Oh.
你好  我本应该先打电话预约再来找你的
Hey, listen. About showing up at your office, I should've called.
是我失礼了
lt was rude of me.
没关系
Okay.
我有请保姆的钱了
l got the money for the babysitter.
你有钱了
You did?
所以我们现在可以告诉法官  我一切都准备好了  是吗
So now we just tell the Judge, and we're all set, right?
好吧  这个  呃  再看吧  我们再看吧
Right. Well, uh... We'll see. We'll see.
- 你好  - 你好
- Hey. - Hey.
我们和木星公司的人会在周五开会
Ah... so we're meeting with the Jupiter people on Friday
仔细聊一聊代言合同的问题
to go over the endorsement deal.
好的
Right. Right.
你给卢卡斯·法尔钱了吗
Did... did you give Lucas Farr, uh... money?
什么
What?
他跟你说了什么吗
What'd he... what'd he say to you?
没有  他只是说从朋友那里借来了一些钱
Well, he just said he got some money from a friend.
我  我没给他钱
l... I didn't give him any money.
好吧  如果你给他钱了  你可能会被要求出庭作证
Well, if you did, you may be asked to testify.
为什么
Why?
法官很关注他财产稳定性的问题
The Judge is concerned about his financial stability.
她需要知道这是一个稳定的收入来源还是其他什么
She's gonna want to know if this is reliable income or just some...
你看到代言合同了吗
Did you have a chance to look at the endorsement contract yet?
- 还没  - 因为弗雷迪·埃文想要股权
- No. - 'Cause Freddy Evans wants equity
要增加百分之三的分红  还有创意自主性
plus three percent revenue plus creative control.
我会再看看的
I'll look over it.
好的  等你有时间再看看  谢了
Yeah. When you get a chance. Thanks.
- 你好  - 你好
- Hey. - Hey.
- 我可以进来吗  - 当然可以
- Can I come in? - Yeah, of course.
所以  呃  你跟尼克说什么了
So uh... what'd you tell Nick?
- 怎么了  - 关于我的  你都跟他说什么了
- What? - About me? Wh-what'd you tell him?
我跟他说我有一个朋友  也是一个律师
l told him that I had a friend who was a lawyer downtown.
什么朋友
What kind of friend?
你知道的  我们经常约会的
You know, that we date occasionally.
我们没有约会
We don't date.
- 我们没有吗  - 当然没有  你是个男的
- We don't? - No. You're a guy.
哦  好吧  那又怎么
Oh, well, so what about...
那  那不一样  我们只是一起呆着
That's-- that's different. That's just something we do.
很抱歉  我并不知道  不知道你没有
I'm sorry. I didn't... I didn't know that you weren't, uh...
我没有什么
That I weren't what?
出柜
Out.
我没有出柜  明白吗
There is nothing to come out of... okay?
绝对没有
Nothing.
好吧  抱歉
Okay. I'm sorry.
好吧
Okay.
我先走了
l gotta go.
杰克  我知道很难为情
Jake, uhm... Iook, l... I know this is...
但是我真的很需要你出庭帮我作证
l really might need you to come to court and help me.
出庭
Come... come to court?
不会要很长时间的
lt won't take very long.
你是疯了吗
Are you outta your mind?
我想说  你认为  你自己想想
l mean, do you think... l mean, if you could think...
你来到我的公司
that just by walking into my firm
你这样会毁了我的工作和生活的
that you might destroy my life and my career!
你想过这个吗
Did you think about that?
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
好吧  呃
Right, uh...
我很抱歉
Sorry.
听着  你要喝点什么吗
Listen, d'you want a drink or something?
你好  尼克  你有时间吗
Hey, Nick. You got a second?
- 我有点忙  - 就一小会
- I'm a little late. - Just come in for a second.
我看过你的合同了
l read your contract.
- 嗯  - 只是  呃
- Yeah. - It's, uh...
整体结构都很好
Overall structure's pretty good,
但是有一些语言上的问题
but I do have a problem with some of the language.
是我给了卢卡斯钱
l gave Lucas the money.
- 好吧  - 嗯
- Right. - Yeah.
昨天晚上  我本来不想的
Uhm... Last night, I didn't want to...
但是这并不是一大笔钱或者多么不得了的大事
You know, it's not that it's a big deal or anything, giving him some money.
我只是觉得  他是一个好孩子  我在努力帮助他而已
l mean, he's a good kid. I'm... trying to help him out, you know?
当然理解
Sure.
我想说  这整件事  我不知道从何说起
l mean, this is, uh... I mean, the whole thing... I don't know where to begin.
杰克  你不需要跟我解释的
Jake, you don't need to explain.
但我不是同性恋
Look, I'm not gay.
- 杰克  - 我真的不是
- Jake... - I'm not.
我为现在的一切付出了太多
I've worked too hard for something like this to happen.
太努力  去避免人们说我是什么死同志
Way too hard... to have people... talking about me like I'm some kind of faggot.
我只是  只是不能让周围的人这样议论我
l... I just... l can't have it around here.
- 我就是  真的不能  - 没关系的
- I just... I just... I can't. - It's okay.
这真的只是偶尔一次
l mean, it's just once in a while.
要知道  这并不关乎爱情或者是其他什么
You know, it's not like... It's not romantic or anything.
这些都与我无关的  杰克
lt's not my business, Jake.
跟卢卡斯的这件事  是大概一个月之前的了
lt just kinda happened about a month ago... with Lucas.
匹兹堡是一个小地方
Pittsburgh's a small town.
没关系的
lt's okay.
不  不是的
No, it's not.
你怎么进来的
How'd you get in here?
进来并不难
lt's not hard.
我真的  只是需要一点钱
l just... I just need a few bucks, is all.
要多少
How much?
就几千美金
Just a few thousand.
我就是  需要去买一些处方药
l just... I need to pay for some prescription drugs.
我得了该死的癌症  药都很贵  真的
l got this damn cancer thing happening and... pills are expensive, is all.
宝贝  我不知道你怎么会这么害怕我
l don't know why l scare you so much, sweetheart.
我只是你的爸爸啊
l mean, I'm just your daddy.
得了吧
Please.
我是你的爸爸啊
I'm just your daddy.
请拿着你的钱  离开这里
Please take your money and leave.
是谁给了卢卡斯请保姆的钱
Who gave Lucas the money for the babysitter?
家里的一个朋友
A family friend.
他在场吗
ls he or she present?
并没有在
Not available, Your Honor.
在作出决定之前我需要先跟他沟通一下
Well, I'll need to speak with him before I make a ruling.
为什么一定要这样
Why is that?
什么
l beg your pardon?
法官阁下 你让我们想出一个解决方案
Your Honor you asked us to come up! with a plan.
他雇了一个保姆
He hired a babysitter.
卢卡斯现在需要更多的钱  那两个月后又会发生什么
And what happens two months from now when Lucas needs more money?
我们需要确定卢卡斯自己可以解决这个问题
We have to trust that Lucas can come up with it on his own.
所以我还是要跟那个人谈一下
Well, I'd still like to speak...
达森法官  您给卢卡斯提了要求 他也按照要求做了
Judge Damsen, you gave Lucas a directive. He followed that through.
法林先生  不要打断我
Mr. Fallin, do not interrupt me.
我很抱歉  我们还是别牵扯无关的人了吧
I'm sorry. Let's not make this about a third party.
法尔先生  这是你的最后一次机会
Mr. Farr, this is your last chance.
你的新律师给我爸爸打电话了
Your new lawyer called my father.
我听说了
l heard.
拜托  杰德  这太荒谬了
Come on, Jed. This is ridiculous.
我们在说这九万三千美元
We're talking about ninety-three thousand dollars.
也许你更应该跟我的律师谈
You should probably be talking to my lawyer about this.
我们可以达成一致的
We can be nice to a point.
你在吓唬我吗
Are you threatening me?
如果我们不能得出解决措施
lf we can't work something out here...
我们就会起诉
we're gonna have to sue,
之后你就得付一大笔律师费
and you're gonna end up spending a lot of money on legal fees
跟付给我们的几乎一样多
as well as paying us.
你父亲每年收了我六万五千美元的信托管理费
Your father charges me sixty-five thousand dollars a year to oversee my Trust.
是六万五千美元啊
Sixty-five thousand dollars
就只是为了审查银行账单  为了一个月打两个电话
to review bank statements... to make two phone calls a month--
这两件事还都是烦人的事
both of which are annoying--
只会告诉我  我不能做什么
to tell me what I can't do,
提醒我  我是个白痴  而我爸是个天才
that I'm an idiot, that my father was a genius.
我爸爸就是那样的人  你是知道他的
Well, that's just my father. You know him.
我破产了
I'm broke.
俱乐部的事都要烦死我了
The Club is killing me.
你欠了多少钱
How much money do you owe?
差不多两百万美元
Almost two million dollars.
如果你真的破产了  撤诉吧  让我们来帮你
lf you're broke, drop the suit. Let us help you.
我付不起
l can't pay.
能试的我都试过了
I've tried.
我也给朋友们打电话了
I've called friends.
我甚至跟银行谈过
l talked to the bank.
但是还是没有钱
l just don't have the money.
经历过强奸指控后  我被解雇了
After the rape charge, I got fired.
我已经透支了
l was already over-extended.
私人学校  新房子
Private school. New house.
现在我也找不到工作  试想一下  谁会雇我呢
Now I can't find a job. l mean, who's gonna hire me?
为什么  他们为什么
Why... why would they?
我可能会坐牢
l might be going to jail.
亚历克斯  尼克和伯顿最关心的是什么
Alex, what Nick and Burton are most concerned with
是制定一些新的付款时间表
is creating some kind of payment schedule.
我现在仅剩的就是我的房子了
Well, all I have left is my house.
还有的妻子  她
And my wife... she doesn't--
她并不知道关于我们经济状况的事情
she doesn't know about my... about our financial situation.
我知道我之前说能付给你们
l know I told you I could pay you,
但是只能是卖了我的房子  我还没有跟我妻子说
but to do that I'd have to sell my house, and I haven't told my wife.
好吧  我现在不想继续这个话题了
All right, look... I'd like to... not continue this right now.
你明天在法庭上会有一场硬仗  我们在审判之后再说这件事吧
You got a tough day in court tomorrow. Why don't we take this up after the trial?
法林先生  我会付给你钱的
Mr. Fallin, I'll pay you.
我保证  我会付给你的
l promise, I'll pay you.
好吧
Well...
好吧  我需要准备明天的开庭了
Well... I have to prepare for tomorrow.
好的  太感谢你了  赛迪
Yeah, thanks, Sadie.
生意难做啊
Tough business.
尼克  你去见杰克了吗
Nick, have you seen Jake?
没有
No.
木星高尔夫球公司的人在会议室等他
Those guys from Jupiter Golf are waiting in the conference room.
我给他打电话了  但是没有人接
l called Jake's cell phone. He's not answering.
好吧
All right.
克鲁切克先生  很抱歉让您等了这么久
Mr. Kruczek. Sorry to keep you waiting.
没事  不急  杰克呢
Oh, no. No worries. Where's Jake?
有一个紧急客户  他很快就会回来
Uh, client emergency. He'll be... he'll be back pretty soon.
我仔细看了你的代言合同
So uh... l, uh, read over your endorsement agreement.
是个好的开始
lt's a good start.
您想来点咖啡吗
You want a coffee?
还是水或者苏打
Water? Soda?
什么都不需要了  谢谢
No, we're good, thanks.
好吧  那么第一个问题就是版税的问题了
Okay. Well, first issue is the royalty payout.
我的助理律师正在整理一些可行的方案
Uh, my paralegal is putting together some comparables right now.
那么  关于奥克芒
So... Oakmont.
我正努力调整一下日程
I'm trying to clear my schedule.
从一个在斯克兰顿的
Have to extricate myself from a wedding...
婚礼中抽身
in Scranton... of all places.
什么时候开球
So what time is tee-off?
- 七点零六  - 好的
- 7:06. - Great.
你的差点指数是多少
What's your handicap?
差点指数  六
Handicap. Six.
六吗  那你可以和专业的一起玩了
Six? You'll play with the pro, then.
是我们配不上你了
You're outta my league.
这个  如果我能不用去那个婚礼的话
Well, that's if I can get out of the wedding.
当然  我很理解  希望到时能见到你
Of course, I understand. Hope to see ya.
- 杰德有信儿了吗  - 没有
- Any word from Jake? - No.
- 给他家打电话了吗  - 打了四次了
- You try his apartment? - Four times.
卢卡斯
Lucas.
一点同志争执罢了
A little bit of fag-bashing.
我猜杰德是想要证明他不是同性恋
l guess Jake wanted to make a point that he's not gay.
是的  他在这吗
Right. Is he here?
没  他已经走了  他喝了很多
No. He's gone. He... he was drinking.
冲进屋子
He came into the apartment.
我们聊了一会  我想我也说了一些气话
We had some words. l said some stupid things, I guess.
所以  抱歉  我得收拾好然后去上班了
So... uh... if you'll excuse me, l have to clean up and get to work.
杰克  嘿  我是尼克
Jake, hey, it's Nick.
一收到消息尽快给我回话
Call me as soon as you get this message on my cell or LSP.
谢谢
Thanks.
穆尼先生  我不知道你是不是清楚
l didn't know if you were aware, Mr. Moloney,
但是杜肯联合银行已经同意接受个人捐款了
but Duquesne Union Bank has agreed to match any personal donation
在我的律所超过五千美金的
made to my clinic that's over five thousand dollars.
好的  我当然也不想听起来不够感恩
Right. And I certainly don't want to sound unappreciative,
但是我注意到  如果你再增加捐款五百元
but I noticed that if you increase your donation by another five hundred,
那我的律所就额外多了五千
then my clinic will get an extra five thousand.
露露
Lulu.
你父刚刚被送到医院了
Your father's just been rushed to the hospital.
莫洛尼先生  我晚点再打给你好吗
Mr. Moloney, can I call you right back?
谢谢
Thanks.
- 什么  - 真的  就在外边街上
- What? - Yeah, out on the street.
他们刚刚把他送上救护车
They just put him in the back of an ambulance,
现在正送去医院
and they're taking him to the hospital.
我可以现在就带你过去
l can take you right down there.
不  不用了  谢谢
No... no, thanks.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
是的  没事的  我会给医院打电话的
Yeah. It's fine. I'll just call over there.
好吧
Okay.
你跟你的父亲提过领养日的事情吗
Did you... did you, um... ever speak to your father about the Adoption Day thing?
嗯  是的  我爸爸  他想跟你一起吃个午餐
Uh, yeah. Yeah, Dad... uh... he wants to have lunch with you.
嗯
Hmm.
有什么我能帮你的吗
ls there anything I can do to help you?
至少现在我知道他在哪  而且也没有人会一直给我打电话  所以
Least now I know where he is, and my phone won't be ringing as much, so...
- 你好  - 你好
- Uh, hey. - Hey.
你怎么在这
What are you doing here?
额  就是你昨天缺席了和木星公司的会  然后  呃
Oh, it's just you... you missed the, uh, Jupiter meeting yesterday, and, uh...
大哥  现在是早上七点
lt's seven o'clock in the morning, man.
是啊
Yeah.
你还好吧
Are you all right?
其实你就是你
Well, you are the way you are.
谁在乎呢  没人在乎
Who cares? Who cares?
这话是什么意思
What the hell does that mean?
- 我的意思是  - 我是什么人
- Well... l... - The way I am?
- 好吧  - 听着  朋友  我不是同性恋
- Okay... - Look... man, I am not gay.
明白吗  这就是你想暗示我的
Okay? If that is what you're implying.
- 明白  - 好了 所以不用这样对我
- Okay. - Okay, so don't treat me
好像我是个需要你同情的家伙
like I'm some guy that you need to pity
或者好像你知道我的事  你什么都不知道
or that you know anything about me, because you don't!
好吧
All right.
我们十点要定下和木星公司的合作
Well, we close the Jupiter deal at ten.
你好
Hey.
我爸爸之前做过一些事
My daddy did some things.
嗯
Okay.
很难说清楚
lt's hard to explain.
我十四岁的时候交了个男朋友
l had this boyfriend when I was fourteen.
他是个足球运动员  很帅
He was a football player. He was cute.
我父亲  那个时候在扬斯敦  也许是在废料场工作
My dad was, uh... was in Youngstown then, l think, working in the scrap yard.
然后  我那时候是个拉拉队长
And, uh... and I was a cheerleader.
而且  当我抬头看看台  就会看到我爸爸
And... I would look up into the stands, and I would see my father.
他就在那盯着我
He would just stare at me...
之后他也会给我留言
and he would leave me notes...
说我有多下贱
about what a whore I was.
之后  呃  有一天晚上
And, uh... one night I was...
我和这个男孩一起
l was with this boy, uh...
我们正走回家  手牵着手
and we were just walking home, you know... holding hands.
我爸喝多了  他开着皮卡过来
My dad was drunk, and he pulled up in his truck,
走了出来  之后  呃
and he got out and, uh...
太恐怖了
lt was terrible.
你好  杰德
Hey, Jed.
伯顿
Burton.
最近怎么样
How ya doing?
要喝点什么吗
Get you something to drink?
嗯  不要了  谢谢
Uh... I don't think so. Thanks.
杰德  你为什么不告诉我这里的情况
Jed, why didn't you, uh... why don't you tell me what's going on here?
然后等你来跟我说你有多明智吗
So you can tell me that you were right?
不
No.
我从来没有反对你看这家俱乐部
l was never against the club.
你就是反对的
Yes, you were.
没有  这只是一个酒吧
No... it's just... a nightclub.
只是风险太大了
That's a risky venture.
不是的  你们家对这一行没有经验
Not a... business your family ever knew anything about.
我只是需要一些时间来让这家店站稳脚跟  仅此而已
l just need a little time to get this place on its feet. That's all.
好吧
Right.
那你能再给我点时间吗
So you'll cut me a break?
杰德  要知道你爸爸和我
Jed, you know, your father and l...
天呐  你出生的时候我就在旁边
Hell, I was at the hospital the day you were born.
我总想着把你当成我的儿子  但是我不能这样
l... I always thought of you as a son, but, uh... I can't do that.
我会撤诉的
I'll drop the suit.
很高兴你这样决定  但是我们也的确需要被付款了
Well, I appreciate that, but, uh... we've got to be paid.
再放任下去实在不行了
lt would not be right to let it slide.
我不相信
l don't believe this.
我已经破产了
I'm broke.
杰德  关了这家店  把能卖的卖了吧
Jed, just close the club down and sell your assets.
相信我  我是在替你着想
Believe me, l... I'll be doing you a favor.
替我想
A favor.
明天来一下办公室
Come by the office tomorrow.
我们会想办法让你东山再起的
We'll figure out some way to get you back on your feet.
我解雇你了  伯顿
l fired you, Burton.
我知道
l know that.
我付不起你钱了
l can't pay you.
嗯  明天来一下吧
Well... just come by the office tomorrow.
宾夕法尼亚联邦政府对亚历克斯·富兰克林·凯勒诉求
ln the matter of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania vs. Alex Franklin Kaller...
指控一  强奸  一级重罪
On charge one: Rape, a felony in the first degree,
陪审团认定被告无罪
we the jury find the defendant Not Guilty.
指控二  恶意伤人  一级重罪
On charge two: Aggravated Assault, a felony in the first degree,
陪审团认定被告无罪
we the jury find the defendant Not Guilty.
赛迪
Sadie.
太谢谢你了
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
尼克
Nick.
恭喜
Congratulations.
我刚刚跟我妻子说过了
l just talked with my wife, and, uh... we can...
我们打算卖掉房子  可以吧
Well, we're gonna sell the house, all right?
我们会全付清的
We're gonna pay this thing off.
好的
Okay.
好的  恭喜了
Okay. Well... congratulations.
听着  我不是
Hey. I'm not...
天呐  卢卡斯  我实在是太抱歉了
God, Lucas, I'm so... I'm sorry.
我的意思是
l mean, I was...
我不能为我做的事找借口
What I did was inexcusable.
听着  我希望你别跟别人说
Look, I hope that we can keep this...
我知道  你有权利做你想做的事情
l mean, you have every right to... to do whatever you want.
我不会报警的  杰克
l... I'm not gonna call the cops, Jake.
谢谢
Thank you.
我是说  你曾经帮助过我
l mean, you helped me.
卢卡斯  听着  我  呃
So Lucas, look, l, uh...
我没办法
l can't... I mean...
即使是你想  我也不能再见你了
Even if you wanted to, l can't see you again.
为什么
Why?
因为  不管这是什么  这  这不是真正的我
Because... whatever this was, it's just... it's just... isn't who I am.
因为你的朋友发现我们的事了
'Cause your friend found out?
不  不是  因为
No. No, because...
好  我会忘了这一切
Right, I forgot.
因为你是直男
Because you're straight.
所以  嗯
So... I mean, uh...
- 你好  - 你好
- Hey. - Hey.
好吧  我这周收了五十万美元的帐
All right, l, uh... collected half a million this week.
好的
Good.
跟理查德·斯坦聊过了
Spoke to Richard Stein.
装病拖欠不还钱的家伙
The Malinger people.
他们付钱了
They paid.
- 全款吗  - 是的
- In full? - Yeah.
那太好了
Yeah. Good.
至于亚历克斯·凯勒的事儿  嗯
As for Alex Kaller, uh...
我觉得我们也许可以做些什么
l thought maybe we could work something out.
赛迪胜诉了  他也给我们提点了
lt's a win for Sadie and he brought Checkpoint to us.
一共十六万美元啊
Ah... it's a hundred and sixty thousand dollars.
是的  但是他已经打算卖掉房子了  爸爸
Yeah, well, he's ready to sell his home, Dad.
但是我们欠银行一百万美金哪
Well, we owe the bank a million dollars.
是的
Right.
所以
So...
好吧
Right.
我们尽快让他付款
We get paid.
赛迪
Sadie.
祝贺你  干得漂亮
Congratulations. Good job.
谢谢
Thank you.
你能跟亚历克斯说  我理解卖掉房子还需要一段时间
Can you tell Alex that, you know, I know it may take some time to sell the house?
没关系的
lt's okay.
- 好的  我会转告他  - 好的
- Right. I will. - Okay.
格雷琴
Gretchen.
- 木星公司的人在吗  - 是的
- The guys from Jupiter Golf in there? - Yeah.
- 那杰德呢  - 我没看见他
- What about Jake? - I didn't see him.
假设一个球跑过了第七果岭  对吧
So supposedly, a turkey ran across the seventh green, right?
一秒钟之后  另一个球从后边追它
A second later a fox comes bolting ou't after it.
刚好超过了厄尼埃尔斯的球
Goes right over Ernie Els' ball.
- 你好  尼克  - 你好
- Hey, Nick. - Hey.
很抱歉  我来晚了
Uh... sorry I'm late.
没事的  我们正聊的开心
No, it's okay. We're, uh... we're good here.
- 我们正要开始  - 太好了
- We're just getting started. - Great.
是的  是的  我们聊得很开心
Yeah. Yeah. We're... we're good here.
杰克
Jake?
我只是  呃
I just, uh...
我只是  嗯
I-- I just, uhm...
杰克  需要我接手吗
Uh, Jake, you want me to take over?
不用了  我们接着聊聊版税结构的问题
No, let's just... let's just talk about royalty structure.
薪水应该是未来版税的预付款
Salary should be an advance against future royalties.
现在他们想要百分之三  我减到了百分之二
Now they wanted three percent. I got 'em down to two percent.
这样我觉得每个人都能满意了
I think everyone's gonna be happy all the way around.
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177